const dataArr = [
    {
        "id": "1",
        "verb": "to be",
        "infinitive_fre": "être",
        "conjugations": [
            {
                "id": "11",
                "answer": ["je suis"],
                "question": "I am"
            },
            {
                "id": "12",
                "answer": ["tu es"],
                "question": "you are"
            },
            {
                "id": "13",
                "answer": ["il/elle/on est", "il est", "elle est", "on est"],
                "question": "he/she/one is"
            },
            {
                "id": "14",
                "answer": ["nous sommes"],
                "question": "we are"
            },
            {
                "id": "15",
                "answer": ["vous êtes"],
                "question": "you are (pl)"
            },
            {
                "id": "16",
                "answer": ["ils/elles sont", "ils sont", "elles sont"],
                "question": "they are"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "verb": "to go",
        "infinitive_fre": "aller",
        "conjugations": [
            {
                "id": "21",
                "answer": ["je vais"],
                "question": "I go"
            },
            {
                "id": "22",
                "answer": ["tu vas"],
                "question": "you go"
            },
            {
                "id": "23",
                "answer": ["il/elle/on va", "il va", "elle va", "on va"],
                "question": "he/she/one goes"
            },
            {
                "id": "24",
                "answer": ["nous allons"],
                "question": "we go"
            },
            {
                "id": "25",
                "answer": ["vous allez"],
                "question": "you go (pl)"
            },
            {
                "id": "26",
                "answer": ["ils/elles vont", "ils vont", "elles vont"],
                "question": "they go"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "verb": "to want",
        "infinitive_fre": "vouloir",
        "conjugations": [
            {
                "id": "31",
                "answer": ["je veux"],
                "question": "I want"
            },
            {
                "id": "32",
                "answer": ["tu veux"],
                "question": "you want"
            },
            {
                "id": "33",
                "answer": ["il/elle/on veut", "il veut", "elle veut", "on veut"],
                "question": "he/she/one wants"
            },
            {
                "id": "34",
                "answer": ["nous voulons"],
                "question": "we want"
            },
            {
                "id": "35",
                "answer": ["vous voulez"],
                "question": "you want (pl)"
            },
            {
                "id": "36",
                "answer": ["ils/elles veulent", "ils veulent", "elles veulent"],
                "question": "they want"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "verb": "to be able",
        "infinitive_fre": "pouvoir",
        "conjugations": [
            {
                "id": "41",
                "answer": ["je peux"],
                "question": "I can"
            },
            {
                "id": "42",
                "answer": ["tu peux"],
                "question": "you can"
            },
            {
                "id": "43",
                "answer": ["il/elle/on peut", "il peut", "elle peut", "on peut"],
                "question": "he/she/one can"
            },
            {
                "id": "44",
                "answer": ["nous pouvons"],
                "question": "we can"
            },
            {
                "id": "45",
                "answer": ["vous pouvez"],
                "question": "you can (pl)"
            },
            {
                "id": "46",
                "answer": ["ils/elles peuvent", "ils peuvent", "elles peuvent"],
                "question": "they can"
            }
        ]
    }
]


export default dataArr